<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YWallet</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/index.html</link><description>YWallet is the most advanced and fastest Crypto Wallet for Zcash and Ycash.
Please use the Navigation Menu to read this documentation.
Don’t forget the SEARCH feature</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/installation/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/installation/index.html</guid><description>Current version: 1.5.4 Platform Link Remarks Android Google Play Store Android APK No dependency on Google Apps iOS App Store Windows ZIP Portable, Just unzip and run Linux AppImage Need GLIB 2.34 Linux Flatpak Requires flatpack runtime Linux Flathub MacOS DMG For both Intel and Apple chips Source Code Github Info The Microsoft Store version is discontinued due to a change of their policy regarding self-custody crypto wallets.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/getting_started/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/getting_started/index.html</guid><description>Press the “New Account” button to get started (whether it is your first time or you already have an old account you want to restore).
Disclaimer Please read the disclaimer then check every box to enable the check mark button.
The app will move to the creation of the first account.
Next Steps New Account Security Select Server Themes Info For maximum privacy, consider running your own server. It is the only way to be 100% sure that the server operator does not collect tracking information.</description></item><item><title>Account Info</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/balance/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/balance/index.html</guid><description>Balance
This page shows information about your selected account. To switch between accounts, use the Account Manager
Synchronization Status Address(es) Balance Send Button The button/message “Backup Missing” is a reminder that you have not visited the Backup Page yet. Tap on it to go to Backup by Seed.</description></item><item><title>Security</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/security/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/security/index.html</guid><description>Unless an account is watch-only, it has the secret keys needed to perform transactions. Therefore it is important to keep your computer/phone away from intruders and malware.
YWallet has several security features that help you prevent loss of funds but be aware that when your device is connected to the Internet there is a level of risk that cannot be avoided.
See Cold Wallet for a way to make transaction while keeping your secret keys on a disconnected device.</description></item><item><title>Transacting</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/transacting/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/transacting/index.html</guid><description>Besides checking your balance, making transactions is the bread and butter of any crypto wallet…</description></item><item><title>Contacts</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/contacts/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/contacts/index.html</guid><description>Contacts
Contacts is an address book that stores names and addresses.
Note Each account has its own address book but the Contacts page combines all the contacts.
When you create a new contact, it is saved in the current account.
List of contacts Button for adding a new contact Button to save contacts to the blockchain Saving your contacts to the blockchain makes a special self-transaction that contains your unsaved contacts.</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/history/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/history/index.html</guid><description>History
This is your transaction history.
It can be displayed in table or list layout.
List Table The table format shows more information and is better suited for larger screen.
You can also sort the columns by clicking on the column headers.
The layout can be selected in the settings
Clicking or tapping on a transaction will navigate to the transaction details.
Warning Transactions that do not involve any shielded input/output, i.</description></item><item><title>Messages</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/messages/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/messages/index.html</guid><description>Messages
With transactions, you can have memos or messages.
Messages are your transaction memos shown in a more friendly way. Like transactions, they can be organized as a list or as a table.
List Table If you have a contact in your address book with the matching address, Ywallet will display the contact name instead of the address.
Also, the list shows your message as a chat. However, some of the messages may not have a known sender.</description></item><item><title>Pools</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/pools/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/pools/index.html</guid><description>More/Pools
Currently there are three pools or types of ZEC:
transparent sapling orchard The last two are shielded.
Funds from any pool are fungible. In other words, you can make a transaction that uses funds from any pool, and pays to any pool. There is no financial difference between them, like there is no difference between the 1 USD note and the 1 USD coin.
However, it does not mean that they have the same properties.</description></item><item><title>Synchronization</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/sync/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/sync/index.html</guid><description>More/Synchronization
After installation, the wallet starts with no data from the blockchain/network.
Synchronization is the process by which the wallet gets the transaction data and updates its database.
There are two types of information:
accounts and keys: only you should know that. synchronization data: derived from the keys and the blockchain data. Light wallets The blockchain has hundreds of GB of data. It contains all the transactions of every user. Therefore it will keep growing larger and larger.</description></item><item><title>Account Manager</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/accounts/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/accounts/index.html</guid><description>More/Accounts
The Account Manager is where you add/edit/delete accounts.
Switch Account To change the current account, tap on its name.
New See new account
Edit/Delete Long press on an account name to enter edit mode. Then you will have the option to rename or delete it.
Note The current account cannot be deleted unless it is the only account remaining. You need to switch to another account.
At the moment, there is no way to reorder accounts.</description></item><item><title>Backup</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/index.html</guid><description>Maintaining a safe backup is extremely important.
Warning Without a backup, your funds are irremediably LOST in case of a hardware or software failure.
Ywallet supports two types of backups:
By seed phrase or secret key By saving an encrypted copy of its database Each has its own benefits and drawbacks. But you should at least have one type of backup.</description></item><item><title>Cold Wallet</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/coldwallet/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/coldwallet/index.html</guid><description>See Cold Storage.
The Cold Wallet feature uses two devices running Ywallet.
the first device has the viewing key and is connected to the Internet. It can synchronize and report the account balance, but it cannot spend the second device has the secret key but is disconnected from the Internet. It can sign transactions prepared on the first device By keeping the secret key on a device that remains offline permanently, the account cannot be hacked by remote access.</description></item><item><title>Market Insights</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/market/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/market/index.html</guid><description>In this section, you will find charts and tables related to your account transaction history and the value of the wallet.
Budget Market Prices</description></item><item><title>MultiPay</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/multipay/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/multipay/index.html</guid><description>MultiPay allows you to create transactions with more than one recipient.
To use it, start by opening the MultiPay Page. Then,
Add Recipients, this will open the Send Page or the Custom Send Page The current recipients will appear here. If you need to delete an item, long press on it then press the delete button Finish up by pressing the send button. You’ll navigate to the Transaction Report as usual.</description></item><item><title>Recovery Tools</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/tools/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/tools/index.html</guid><description>The Recovery Tools help you import accounts from other wallet apps. They require some knowledge of the key derivation mechanism.
Here is a brief recap on the topic.
Transparent Wallet Let’s consider a typical Zcash transparent wallet. It supports multiple currencies, all under the same seed phrase.
Derivation Path From a given seed phrase, you can derive lots of keys using a set of rules and a “path”.
A path looks like a directory path except that each component is an integer.</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/settings/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/settings/index.html</guid><description/></item><item><title>Security &amp; Audit</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/audit/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/audit/index.html</guid><description>YWallet went through two security reviews conducted by
Taylor Hornby (former ECC employee and Zcash Protocol Engineer); Least Authority. Both following grants from the Zcash Community Grants
Reports The reports are available for download:
Ywallet Security and Privacy Analysis ZCG Consultation Feedback Disclosure If you find a security issue, please report it to the author via email to Ywallet Email
For encrypted communication, use the following AGE public key age1ys5w8jljape5nr40n4gg2zfh6a5tf4eq6xfsftlw8dmnnfeczd3q2pqgnd</description></item><item><title>Maya Protocol / Zcash</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/maya/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/maya/index.html</guid><description>This document serves both as an introduction to the integration project of Zcash/ZEC into Maya Protocol (MP) and a technical feasibility study. In the first, we describe the architecture of MP and the workflows for deposit/withdraw and swap.
Next, we’ll discuss how to add ZEC as a new chain which will allow the creation of the liquidity pool ZEC.
We aim to have transparent &amp; shielded ZEC available both as a source and a destination of a swap.</description></item><item><title>QR</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/qr/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/qr/index.html</guid><description>Save Copy the QR code to the clipboard Save the QR code as a PNG image file Scan</description></item></channel></rss>