<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Backup :: YWallet</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/index.html</link><description>Maintaining a safe backup is extremely important.
Warning Without a backup, your funds are irremediably LOST in case of a hardware or software failure.
Ywallet supports two types of backups:
By seed phrase or secret key By saving an encrypted copy of its database Each has its own benefits and drawbacks. But you should at least have one type of backup.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seed &amp; Keys</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/seed/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/seed/index.html</guid><description>Saving the seed phrase is the #1 way to save your account. It is compatible with most wallet apps, i.e. you can recover your funds using another wallet than Ywallet.
However, every account has its own seed phrase and you MUST save every seed phrase if you have multiple accounts.
Moreover, the seed phrase saves your account keys but not the synchronizationd data. After you recover, you will have to rescan the blockchain from the account height.</description></item><item><title>App Backup</title><link>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/app/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hhanh00.github.io/ywdocs/backup/app/index.html</guid><description>App Backup is a compressed &amp; encrypted copy of the application database.
It contains all the account and the synchronization data.
By restoring from an app backup, you will only have to catchup from the point the backup was made.
This can be a huge time saver, especially if you have several accounts.
Generating a keypair The backup is encrypted using the AGE software suite. Before you can make a backup, you need to generate a keypair.</description></item></channel></rss>