<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Settings on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/settings/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Settings on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/settings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>General</title><link>https://ywallet.app/settings/general/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/settings/general/index.html</guid><description>Display amounts in zats or millis. There are 100 000 000 zats per ZEC. Use Custom Send by default Reference Currency Default Memo Currency Use one of the supported FIAT currency or Crypto (BTC, ETH, etc.)
Custom Send Custom Send can be configured to show/hide the fields you want. See View.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>https://ywallet.app/settings/privacy/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/settings/privacy/index.html</guid><description>Protect Open and Send with the device lock screen Minimum Privacy Level. Transaction below this level are blocked and need user confirmation to override Fetch transaction details for memo and outgoing addresses Hide/Show the account Balance on the Main Account Page Minimum Number of Confirmations before a note can be spent Encrypt the database with a password (only available on Desktop. Mobile devices always encrypt the db) Transaction Details Getting the transaction details reveals your transaction ids to the remote server.</description></item><item><title>View</title><link>https://ywallet.app/settings/view/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/settings/view/index.html</guid><description>Show Messages as a Table, a List or based on the device orientation Show Transaction History as a Table, a List or based on the device orientation Show Unspent Notes as a Table, a List or based on the device orientation Custom Send Open the field selection page for the Custom Send.</description></item><item><title>Coin</title><link>https://ywallet.app/settings/coin/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/settings/coin/index.html</guid><description>The Anti-Spam filter excludes the processing of large transactions that occurred during the spam period of 2023-2024. Calculate the fee automatically using ZIP-317 rules (highly recommended). You transaction may get stuck if the fees are too low Server Ping each server and get the latency URL of the block explorer Receivers included in the main address Receivers included in the reply-to address (used when you decide to include your address in a message) Receivers used when sending to a UA.</description></item><item><title>Theme</title><link>https://ywallet.app/settings/theme/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/settings/theme/index.html</guid><description> Choose dark/light variant Predefined color schemes</description></item></channel></rss>