<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Transacting on YWallet</title><link>https://ywallet.app/transacting/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Transacting on YWallet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ywallet.app/transacting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Receive</title><link>https://ywallet.app/transacting/receive/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/transacting/receive/index.html</guid><description>To receive funds, you can either give your wallet address or make a Payment URI.
With Zcash, the choice of the address is important because it determines where the funds will arrive.
Ywallet can show several types of addresses, as described in the address section.
In short,
if the sender has a wallet that supports Unified Addresses, use them. if it supports Sapling addresses (zs), use that instead. finally, if it only supports transparent addresses, use the t-addr.</description></item><item><title>Send</title><link>https://ywallet.app/transacting/send/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/transacting/send/index.html</guid><description>To make a simple payment, you will need to know:
the recipient address, the amount. Press the send button at the bottom right corner of the account info page to open up the Send Form.
Addresses are practically never entered manually. They are either copy/pasted, scanned, or taken from the contact list.
The buttons (3) on the right side of the address will respectively:
open the QR scanner ask you to pick up a contact ask you to select one of the accounts (for account to account transfers) Note If the address is shielded, an encrypted memo can be added to the transaction.</description></item><item><title>Transaction Report</title><link>https://ywallet.app/transacting/report/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ywallet.app/transacting/report/index.html</guid><description>The Transaction Report gives you a summary of the transaction BEFORE it gets signed and broadcasted to the network.
Warning This is your final opportunity to check that everything is alright before the transaction becomes irreversible.
Output section. This shows every address you are sending funds to, by address and amount. If you are sending to a unified address, you can see what receiver was chosen. Summary of the source of funds by pool.</description></item></channel></rss>